Guide to the Creative Time Records MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibitions and Projects, 1974-2012; 204.08 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 75 manuscript boxes, 275 jewel cases, 22 box binders, 8 oversized flat boxes, 9 oversized folders, 5 shared record cartons, 2 tall manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 shared flat box, and 1 shared casset
  - The Fear of Disclosure Project: Out in Silence and Not a Simple Story by Christine Choy, June 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 216, Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 135, Folder 21-23)
  - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress by Hunter Reynolds, June-July 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 217-218, Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 8-9)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Sleeve 6)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Institute of Contemporary Art Boston (Box 150, Dvd 179.0511)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Institute of Contemporary Art Boston (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0510)
  - Dyke TV -- Video Recording -- Original -- "Best of Winter", 1994 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0516)
  - 42nd Street Art Project by Multiple Artists, July-September 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 220-228, Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Sleeves 10-19)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- NPR Coverage (Box 145, Cd 179.0106)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- PBS MacNeil/Lehrer Report (Box 149, Dvd 179.0475)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- NPR Coverage (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0105)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- PBS MacNeil/Lehrer Report (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0474)
  - Art in the Anchorage 11: Mirage by Ann Carlson, July-September 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 229-330, Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 10-11)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Sleeves 26-30)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Rebecca Bollinger -- Alphabetically Sorted (Box 146, Dvd 179.0202)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Rebecca Bollinger -- Alphabetically Sorted (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0201)
  - First Annual Sara D. Roosevelt Park Summer Festival by Multiple Artists, July 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 232, Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 14-15)
    - Slides (Box 124, Folder Sleeves 7-9)
  - Lincoln Center Out of Doors: Wild Style by Multiple Artists, August 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 233, Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 16-17)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Norman Salant -- "Saxophone Stories", October 1992 (Box 144, Cd 179.0066)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Norman Salant -- "sax/on" and "After Ours" -- Part 1 (Box 144, Cd 179.0060)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Norman Salant -- "sax/on" and "After Ours" -- Part 2 (Box 144, Cd 179.0061)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Norman Salant -- "Saxophone Stories", October 1992 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0065)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Norman Salant -- "sax/on" and "After Ours" (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0059)
  - Combat Zone: Campaign HQ Against Domestic Violence by Mary Beth Edelson, October-December 1994
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 234, Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 135, Folder 18-19)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 3-4)
  - Citywide, November 1994
    - Correspondence and Guidelines (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Negro Art Collective -- Poster Campaign -- Negative (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Master Builder by Multiple Artists, December 1994 (Box 5, Folder 219, Box 40, Folder 28, Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0691-179.0692)
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 219, Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Kyong Park -- "Detroit: Making it Better For You" (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0692)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Kyong Park -- "Architecture of Resistance" (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0691)
  - Day Without Art -- Programs and Press, December 1994 (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - Barney's New York Window Project -- Correspondence and Press, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Alternative Art Spaces -- Photographs, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Press -- General, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - Cyberwide Virtual Arts Residency by Multiple Artists -- Correspondence and Programs, February 1995 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Artists in Wonderlab by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Sony Plaza -- Correspondence, Programs, and Press, May 1995 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Manhattan Passport: 7 Two-Token Tours by Multiple Artists -- Programs, May 1995 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Relax. Fly Mass Transit by Darrell Wilks, May 1995
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeve 6)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0697)
  - Time Capsule: A Concise Encyclopedia by Women Artists -- Edited by Robin Kahn, 1995-1996
    - Correspondence and Programs (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 25-27)
  - Building Sweeps by Michael Bramwell, June 1995-June 1996
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 21-24)
  - Mama, I Thought Only Black People Were Bad by Negro Art Collective (Tony Cokes, Renée Cox, and Fo Wilson), July 1995
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeve 5)
  - Brinca Charcos (High Waters) by Jennifer Monson -- Co-Presented with El Puente, July-August 1995
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 15-17)
  - Café Bizzoso by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Loisaida Arts -- Correspondence and Programs, July-August 1995 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Art in the Anchorage 12: Affirmative Actions: Artists at Work by Multiple Artists, July-September 1995
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 5, Folder 241, Box 41, Folder 11, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Prints (Box 136, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 7-14)
  - Deviant Craft by W. David Hancock -- Co-Presented by the Foundry Theatre -- Programs and Press, July-August 1995 (Box 41, Folder 10, Box 5, Folder 242)
  - Lincoln Center Out of Doors: DJ Spooky, August 1995
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 18-20)
  - Vintage: Families of Value by Thomas Allen Harris, 1995-1996
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 5, Folder 243, Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 147, Dvd 179.0256)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Heaven Earth and Hell (Box 148, Dvd 179.0366)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Heaven Earth and Hell (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0365)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0255)
  - Day Without Art: Action Project by Multiple Artists -- Programs and Press, December 1995 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Projects in which Creative Time Did Not Participate (includes the Miami Arts Project), 1995
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 42, Folder 6, Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeve 28)
  - Rent a Body by Paco Cao, February-July 1996
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 244, Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Print (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeve 15)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy (Box 144, Cd 179.0010)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Carol and Marylyn TV Talk Show (Box 149, Dvd 179.0467)
    - Audio Recording -- Original (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0009)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Carol and Marylyn TV Talk Show (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0466)
  - "Life, Sex, and Death in a Digital World" -- Co-Presented by The New School and Thread Waxing Space -- Postcard, April 1996 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Money Amok! by Circus Amok! -- Programs, June 1996 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Art in the Anchorage 13 by Multiple Artists, June-August 1996
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
    - Slides (Box 125, Folder Sleeves 29-31)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- EAR and Harmony Rockets (Box 146, Dvd 179.0216)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- VAPP 1995 Application -- Various Artists (Box 147, Dvd 179.0262)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Pierrick Sorin -- "A Very Full Life" (Box 146, Dvd 179.0158)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- EAR and Harmony Rockets (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0215)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- VAPP 1995 Application -- Various Artists (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0261)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Pierrick Sorin -- "A Very Full Life" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0157)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Pierrick Sorin -- "C'est Mignon toutsa" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0143)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- D.A. Therrien -- Pandaemonium -- BBC (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0693)
  - Music in the Anchorage by Multiple Artists, July 1996
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeves 1-7)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Ben Neill -- Part 1 (Box 144, Cd 179.0034)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Ben Neill -- Part 2 (Box 144, Cd 179.0035)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Vernon Reid -- Part 1 (Box 144, Cd 179.0037)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Vernon Reid -- Part 2 (Box 144, Cd 179.0038)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Ben Neill (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0033)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Vernon Reid (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0036)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Demo Reel (Box 146, Dvd 179.0156)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Demo Reel (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0155)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Emergency Broadcast Network -- Video Press Kit (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0680)
  - Race for the Arts by the X-Cheerleaders, September 1996
    - Programs and Press (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeves 8-11)
  - Citywide -- Guidelines and Correspondence, circa 1996 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Day With(out) Art Web Action 1996 by CB Cooke -- Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Holiday Buffet by Elaine Tin Nyo -- Postcard, December 1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Winter Music by Phil Kline -- Co-Presented by Ice Theatre of New York, December 1996
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Folder: Sleeves 12-14)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy (Box 144, Cd 179.0073)
    - Audio Recording -- Original (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0072)
  - The Home Show: Exploring the American Dream -- Unrealized Project -- Proposal and Correspondence, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 8, Box 45, Folder 1)
  - DJ-O-RAMA at Gramercy International Art Fair -- Flyer, May 1997 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Citywide -- Guidelines and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Art in the Anchorage 14: Plug In! by Multiple Artists, June-August 1997
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 45, Folder 4-6)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeves 21-22)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Adrianne Wortzel -- Proposal (Box 144, Cd 179.0071)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Julia Meltzer and Amanda Ramos -- Chatlandia, 3 Conversations (Box 145, Cd 179.0118)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Adrianne Wortzel -- Proposal (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0070)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Julia Meltzer and Amanda Ramos -- Chatlandia, 3 Conversations (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0117)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Adrianne Wortzel -- Technoseduction Exhibition, My Robotic, The Ship's Detective -- Projection Installation (Box 146, Dvd 179.0160)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Rough Footage (Box 146, Dvd 179.0170)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Adrianne Wortzel -- Technoseduction Exhibition, My Robotic, The Ship's Detective -- Projection Installation (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0159)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Rough Footage (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0169)
  - Music in the Anchorage by Multiple Artists, June 1997
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 45, Folder 7, Box 46, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeves 16-20)
  - Olá Suerte Drum Corps Performance and Workshop -- Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors Playday -- Press and Programs, August 1997 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - That Big Yellow Braid by Duston Spear -- Co-Presented by University Settlement House -- Press, August 1997 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Oh…A Fifty Year Dart by Multiple Artists -- Press and Program, September 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Exquisite Corpses by Multiple Artists, September-December 1997
    - Programs and Press (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeve 25)
  - World Views by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented with Deutsche Bank, September-December 1997
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeve 24)
  - Meat Market Art Fair Participant -- Postcard, November 1997 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Silent Orpheus by Plaintext Players -- World AIDS Day -- Program and Press, December 1997 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Day With(out) Art Web Action by Multiple Artists -- Correspondence, December 1997 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - The Wish Machine by Chrysanne Stathacos, December 1997
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeve 23)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- India 2026 and The Wish Machine (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0683)
  - Rumeurs–Les Avatars by Magali Claude, December 1997-1998
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tiems. Toi droit, Les Gestes du Travail, and La Chora. Les rumours (Box 149, Dvd 179.0491)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tiems. Toi droit, Les Gestes du Travail, and La Chora. Les rumours (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0490)
  - Mechanical Marvels: Invention in the Age of Leonardo -- Artists' Gallery Talks -- Flyer, January-February 1998 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 1-900-ALL-KAREN by Karen Finley, February-August 1998
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Flyers (Box 5, Folder 245, Box 47, Folder 8-9)
    - Hat (Box 85)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeve 27)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- "A Message From..." (Box 145, Cd 179.0090)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Cd 179.0004)
    - Audio Recording -- Original (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0003)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- "A Message From..." (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0089)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- "A Message From..." (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0122)
  - Gesture as Value by Jerelyn Hanrahan, May 1998
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 126, Folder Sleeve 28)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- BBC Coverage (Box 147, Dvd 179.0304)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 147, Dvd 179.0306)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- BBC Coverage (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0303)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0305)
  - El Mexterminator by Guillermo Gómez-Peña with Roberto Sifuentes and Sara Shelton Mann
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
    - Slides (Box 127, Folder Sleeves 1-25)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy (Box 145, Cd 179.0112)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- WBAI -- "Voices Against the Wall" -- Part 1 (Box 145, Cd 179.0100)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- WBAI -- "Voices Against the Wall" -- Part 2 (Box 145, Cd 179.0101)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- WBAI -- "Voices Against the Wall" (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0099)
    - Audio Recording -- Original (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0111)
  - Art in the Anchorage 15 by Multiple Artists, June 1998
    - Correspondence, Photographs, Press, and Programs (Box 48, Folder 5-6, Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 127, Folder Sleeves 26-35)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Detroit Techno (Box 146, Dvd 179.0162)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Standard and Poor -- "Big Night Out" (Box 146, Dvd 179.0168)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Detroit Techno (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0161)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Standard and Poor -- "Big Night Out" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0167)
  - Between Dreams and History by Shimon Attie, October-November 1998
    - Electronic Records, October-November 1998; cuid40894
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 5, Folder 246, Box 49, Folder 3-5, Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 128, Folder Sleeves 1-4)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- "Tribute to Joe Papp" (Box 145, Cd 179.0081)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- "Tribute to Joe Papp" (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0080)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy-- Installation -- Directed by Christopher Beaver (Box 150, Dvd 179.0531)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Installation -- Directed by Christopher Beaver (Box 150, Dvd 179.0535)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy-- BBC Coverage (Box 150, Dvd 179.0533)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Installation -- Directed by Christopher Beaver (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0530)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Installation -- Directed by Christopher Beaver (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0534)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- BBC Coverage (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0532)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Between Dreams and History: The Making of Shimon Attie's Public Art Projects" -- Directed by Christopher Beaver (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0666)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Ludlow Show Master (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0611)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Rivington Show A (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0613)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Rivington Show B (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0612)
  - Suits: The Clothes That Make the Man by The Art Guys with Todd Oldham -- Co-Presented by Target, November 1998
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
    - Slides (Box 128, Folder Sleeves 5-20)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 150, Dvd 179.0573)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 150, Dvd 179.0579)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CBS Coverage (Box 150, Dvd 179.0583)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Fashion TV Coverage (Box 150, Dvd 179.0581)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- CBS Coverage (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0582)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Fashion TV Coverage (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0580)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0572)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0578)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- The Art Guys -- Haverford (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0610)
  - Meat Market Art Fair Participant -- Postcard, November 1998 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Day With(out) Art 1998: The Banner Project and 10 Web Action Tours by Multiple Artists, December 1998
    - Electronic Records, December 1998; cuid40899
    - Correspondence and Press (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Slides (Box 128, Folder Sleeve 21)
  - Swatch Project -- Unrealized -- Correspondence and Proposal, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Adolescence by Ange Leccia -- Co-Presented by Clinica Aesthetica, April 1999
    - Correspondence, Press, Programs, and Photographs (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Slides (Box 129, Folder Sleeve 24)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Sabatina (Box 148, Dvd 179.0411)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- ISA (Box 148, Dvd 179.0380)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 148, Dvd 179.0360)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Sabatina (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0410)
    - Video Recording -- Original-- ISA (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0379)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0359)
  - Art in the Anchorage 16: Exposing Meaning in Fashion Through Presentation by Multiple Artists, May-July 1999
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 51, Folder 3-5, Box 52, Folder 1-2)
    - Negative (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Slides (Box 128, Folder Sleeves 22-32)
    - New York City of Parks and Recreation Department -- Contract Drawings (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Loud and Unhinged -- Film Video Looped (Box 147, Dvd 179.0300)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Loud and Unhinged (Box 145, Dvd 179.0126)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Loud and Unhinged -- Fashion Video Looped (Box 147, Dvd 179.0298)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Standard and Poor -- Carpet Rollers -- Park Restaurant (Box 146, Dvd 179.0250)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Susan Cianciolo -- Diadel (Box 146, Dvd 179.0182)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Loud and Unhinged -- Film Video Looped (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0299)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Loud and Unhinged (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0125)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Loud and Unhinged -- Fashion Video Looped (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0297)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Loud and Unhinged -- Art Video Looped (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0301)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Standard and Poor -- Carpet Rollers -- Park Restaurant (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0249)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Susan Cianciolo -- Diadel (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0181)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Susan Cianciolo -- Run 3 Fashion Show (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0679)
  - Music in the Anchorage by Multiple Artists, June 1999
    - Electronic Records, June 1999; cuid40900
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 129, Folder Sleeves 10-16)
  - F.R.E.D. (Freedom Rules Every Democracy) Art Actions, November 1999
    - Correspondence, Programs, Stickers, and Photographs (Box 52, Folder 4, Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 129, Folder Sleeves 17-23)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- F.R.E.D. Projections -- Shot by Roberto Guerra (Box 151, Dvd 179.0625)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- F.R.E.D. Projections -- Shot by Roberto Guerra (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0624)
  - The Intruder -- Slides, 1999 (Box 129, Folder Sleeve 25)
  - Day With(out) Art 1999: Banner Project, Daily Dispatch, and Web Action by Multiple Artists, December 1999
    - Electronic Records, December 1999; cuid40901
    - Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Citywide -- Electronic Records, 1999; cuid40931
  - Leap by Chris Doyle, April 2000
    - Correspondence, Photographs, Programs, and Press (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
    - Negative (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Slides (Box 129, Folder Sleeves 26-27)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Interviews (Box 149, Dvd 179.0457)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0455)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 150, Dvd 179.0515)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Demo (Box 149, Dvd 179.0451)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 149, Dvd 179.0449)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- December (Box 149, Dvd 179.0453)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Interviews (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0456)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0514)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0454)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0448)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- December (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0448)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Demo (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0450)
  - Teleport Diner by Multiple Artists -- Brooklyn, New York and Stockholm, Sweden, May 2000
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 1-2)
  - Tibor in Orbit by Tibor Kalman -- Co-Presented by The New Museum and Maira Kalman, May-August 2000
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Negatives (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Slides (Box 129, Folder Sleeve 28)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 148, Dvd 179.0352)